KENDALL CLARK

Kendallclarkdev@gmail.com | 213-399-3200 | Sherman Oaks, CA 91403

https://kendallclarkdev.github.io/Kendall-Clark-portfolio/

Summary

Hello!! I'm a Ux/UI Designer with a talent for Making User-centered Designs from Phone Apps to web pages. With a strong knowledge of User Research and Prototyping as well As Building/Coding . I am very communicative and team-oriented with proficiency in HTML/CSS/JS with a Proven history of fostering Planning and design to meet team, individual and management objectives.

Skills

Time management
Project planning
Web Development(HTML5/CSS/Javascript)
User-centered Design
User Experience (UX)
User Research

Front-end Development Adobe XD, Figma, Sketch Teamwork Communication Usability testing Critical thinking

Experience

Front-End Web Developer | Domecity tv (Podcast) - Remote | 07/2021 - 08/2021

Created successful websites that met requirements for objectives such as load speed and design. Collaborated with customers to determine needs and work through design options. Gathered, defined and translated client requirements into product stories and actionable tasks. Monitored website performance to quickly rectify front-end-related issues.

Social Media Manager | Dental For You - Dallas, TX | 10/2018 - 08/2019

Develop, implement and manage our social media strategy

Brought mock-ups to life with HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Define most important social media KPIs

Manage and oversee social media content

Measure the success of every social media campaign

Stay up to date with latest social media best practices and technologies

Use social media marketing tools such as Buffer.

UI Lead Designer | Career Carrot Remote | 08/2021 - 09/2021

plan and implement new designs

Optimize existing user interface designs

Test for intuitivity and experience

Communicate with clients to understand their business goals and objectives

Develop technical and business requirements and always strive to deliver intuitive and user-centered solutions

Combine creativity with an awareness of the design elements

Create prototypes for new product ideas

Education and Training

Northside High School | Warner Robins, GA | 05/2014

High School Diploma

<u>Northwest University</u> | Kirkland, WA **Some College (No Degree)**: Social Psychology

<u>General Assembly</u> | Los Angeles, CA | Expected in 11/2021 **User**

Experience Design: Ux/UI Design